plancessjee.com 2016-06-01

# Privacy Policy | Plancess

[Plancess.com](https://www.plancess.com/) is an online JEE Main & Advanced / AIPMT / Foundation coaching portal with the constant motivation to provide you with premium quality educational material in terms of [high quality IIT Video Lectures](https://www.plancess.com/products/iit-jee-video-lectures-pcm) and [ Study Materials](https://www.plancess.com/products/iit-jee-study-material-pcm). We are strongly committed to the right to privacy and we have drawn a privacy statement that protects the information we collect from you.

Kindly read this privacy policy thoroughly so that you may learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information.

We use a SECURED SERVER for all credit card transactions that protects credit card information of our clients. We have enabled cookies to store login information.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions at the registration process and by visiting and using the Site, you have expressly consented to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Our web portal incorporates various communication ways like email address, first and last name, mobile number, etc. We are committed to gather only that information which we will require to help serve you better.

Our Privacy Policy does not allow us to disclose any information with any third party. Your personal information in any manner will be secured under our privacy policy.

All users across India and abroad can browse our site free of cost for searching any course, faculty, article or feature offered by our web portal. You are liable to pay only when you purchase/renew the course/courses.

The plancess.com has trained staff members who may contact you for either services or sales through various communication mediums provided by you in your personal information like mobile number, landline number and email address i.e. via email, phone call or text messages.
